Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 8 Month(s)

Highest Degree: M.Tech [Computers]

Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period



Innovation Associate, Full Stack Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Web Development, Requirement Gathering, Python, Pandas, NumPy, SciKit, HTML, CSS, SQL, ReactJS, REST APIs, Django, Jira



Current Designation: Innovation Associate, Full Stack

Developer

Current Company: ATA Freight India Pvt. Ltd

Current Location: Pune

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Mumbai, Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: Courier/Transportation/Freight

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Full Stack Developer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Web

Development, Requirement Gathering, Project Management, Database Design, Python, Panda, HTML, CSS, SQL, React. Js,

Javascript, Django, MySQL, Rest Api, Ajax, JQuery

Verified: Phone Number 1 Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

A technology oriented professional with 2+ years of experience in Software Development in designing and developing web applications using Python, Django Framework..

Experienced Associate with a demonstrated history of working in the logistics industry.

Strong communication skills with an ability to grasp new things quickly, which was conducive to constructive relationships with Product manager and other team members.

Motivated to learn, grow and excel in the IT industry

Work Experience

ATA Freight India Pvt. Ltd as Innovation Associate, Full Stack Developer Oct 2018 to Till Date

Designed and developed a web application using Python and Django Web Framework.

Alternated between front-end and back-end development duties, fulfilling full stack development commitments on projects.

Performed pre-release and live diagnostic testing, eliminating bugs and security flaws from in development and extant product release.

Deployed projects on in-house / cloud Server.

Worked with Python libraries like Numpy, Pandas, SciKit-learn, Scipy, MatplotLib.

Experience in building REST API using Django Rest-Framework.

Good knowledge of regression and classification algorithms as we have built a module in our project.

Developed a single page web application using ReactJs.

CoperByte Software Solutions PVT.LTD as Java Developer Intern

Apr 2018 to Sep 2018

Responsible for developing, designing database structure and integration of project modules.

Developed a window based application for Inventory Management using Swing.

Developed a web application using Servlet, JSP.

Used MySQL Query Browser for creating, executing, and optimizing queries in a graphical environment

Rashtriya Junior College as Teaching Assistant Oct 2015 to Apr 2017

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from G.H. Raisoni College of Engg, Amravati University in 2013

PG: M.Tech (Computers) from Sipna Shikshan Prasarak Mandals College of Engineering and Technology Amravati, Amravati in 2015

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Diploma in Computer Engineering

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Python, Django Web Framework, Java, SQL			
HTML, CSS, Bootstrap			
JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax, ReactJS			
MySQL, mariadb			
Visual Studio Code, Atom			
NetBeans, Pycharm			
WINDOWS, LINUX			
VirtualBox, MySQL			
Workbench, Git/GitHub			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Hindi	Expert			
Marathi	Expert			

Affirmative Action

Job Type: Permanent

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization